Vance Randolph collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1: Manuscript Materials
  - Subject Files
    - Moonshine liquor., Contains a newspaper clipping, and a handwritten note dealing with moonshiners. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Tom P. Morgan. Folder 1 of 2., Contains newspaper clippings, correspondence, and handwritten and typed notes, dealing with humorist and newspaper columnist Tom P. Morgan. (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Tom P. Morgan. Folder 2 of 2., Contains typed notes. (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Mysterious lights., Contains a typescript about the sightings of unexplained lights in northeastern Oklahoma. (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Names and nicknames. Folder 1 of 2., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, dealing with distinctive names and nicknames of the Ozarks. (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Names and nicknames. Folder 2 of 2., Contains index cards. (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - "The Nobility of the Mountaineer.", Contains typed notes about the character and nature of people living in the rural Ozarks. (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Nonsense speeches., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, dealing with nonsense speeches and illiterate elocutionists. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Old customs. Folder 1 of 2., Contains typed and handwritten notes and typescripts dealing with traditional Ozark social customs. (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Old customs. Folder 2 of 2., Contains newspaper clippings, articles, and correspondence. (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Old Man Burgess., Contains correspondence and a handwritten note dealing with the faith healer J.W. Burgess. (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Outlawry., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, and brochure about the Eureka Springs 1922 bank robbery and famous male and female outlaws. (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Ozark eccentrics., Contains newspaper clippings, brochure, and typed and handwritten notes about interesting Americans and Ozark eccentrics. (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Ozark life., Contains newspaper clippings, correspondence, and typed and handwritten notes about returning to the land. Also includes two typescripts, "Christmas in the Ozarks" and "The Lure of the Ozarks." (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - "Ozarks, Where Are You?" Folder 1 of 2., Contains newspaper clippings and typed and handwritten notes concerning the size of the Ozarks. (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - "Ozarks, Where Are You?" Folder 2 of 2., Contains correspondence and a typescript for an article entitled "Ozarks, Where Are You?" (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Place names. Folder 1 of 6., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, and correspondence. The folder is subdivided into the following subjects: A-L; M-Z; Correspondence. Guide for Students; History and Origin; Listing; Mountains. (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Place names. Folder 2 of 6., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes. Includes: Guide for Students; History and Origin. (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Place names. Folder 3 of 6., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes. Included: Listing; Pronunciation; Mountains; Waterways. (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Place names. Folder 4 of 6., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, and correspondence. Includes: Missouri Barry County; Missouri MacDonald County (photocopy). (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Place names. Folder 5 of 6., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes. Includes: Missouri MacDonald County (original). (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Place names. Folder 6 of 6., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, and correspondence. Includes notes and index cards. (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Politics., Contains newspaper clippings about politics. (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Randolph, Vance. Biographical Material., Contains newspaper and magazine clippings dealing with the life and work of Vance Randolph. (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Randolph, Vance. Book Reviews. Folder 1 of 4., Contains newspaper and magazine clippings and correspondence dealing with reviews of Vance Randolph's books. Includes: Correspondence; The Devil's Pretty Daughter. (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Randolph, Vance. Book Reviews. Folder 2 of 4., Contains newspaper and magazine clippings and correspondence dealing with reviews of Vance Randolph's books. Includes: Down in the Holler; Hot Springs and Hell; Lists; Ozark Folksongs. (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Randolph, Vance. Book reviews. Folder 3 of 4., Contains newspaper and magazine clippings and correspondence dealing with reviews of Vance Randolph's books. Includes: Ozark Superstitions; Sticks in the Knapsack; The Talking Turtle. (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Randolph, Vance. Book Reviews. Folder 4 of 4., Contains newspaper and magazine clippings and correspondence dealing with reviews of Vance Randolph's books. Includes: The Talking Turtle; We Always Lie to Strangers; Who Blowed Up the Church House? (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Randolph, Vance. Scrapbook pages. Folder 1 of 8. Photocopy A. (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Randolph, Vance. Scrapbook pages. Folder 2 of 8. Original A., Contains scrapbook pages with mounted newspaper clippings, dealing primarily with reviews of Vance Randolph's books. (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Randolph, Vance. Scrapbook pages. Folder 3 of 8. Photocopy B. (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Randolph, Vance. Scrapbook pages. Folder 4 of 8. Original B., Contains scrapbook pages with mounted newspaper clippings, dealing primarily with reviews of Vance Randolph's books. (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Randolph, Vance. Scrapbook pages. Folder 5 of 8. Photocopy C. (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Randolph, Vance. Scrapbook pages. Folder 6 of 8. Original C. books., Contains scrapbook pages with mounted newspaper clippings, dealing primarily with reviews of Vance Randolph's books. (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Randolph, Vance. Scrapbook pages. Folder 7 of 8. Photocopy D. (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Randolph, Vance. Scrapbook pages. Folder 8 of 8. Original D., Contains scrapbook pages with mounted newspaper clippings, dealing primarily with reviews of Vance Randolph's books. (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - Reading lists, annotated. Folder 1 of 2., Contains annotated notebooks kept by Vance Randolph listing books he read. The folder is subdivided into the following groups: 1/1/1916 - 9/?/1919; 5/25/1919 - 11/29/1919. (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Reading lists, annotated. Folder 2 of 2., Contains annotated notebooks kept by Vance Randolph listing books he read. The folder is subdivided into the following groups: 2/1/1920 - 12/30/1920; 1/1/1921 - 9/8/1921. (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Religion. Folder 1 of 3., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, and correspondence dealing with religious expression in the Ozarks. Includes: Articles; bibliographic notes; sect name list. Correspondence; notes; sect name list; stories. (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Religion. Folder 2 of 3., Includes: Correspondence; stories. Contains a two-page typescript entitled "Relative to Religion." (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Religion. Folder 3 of 3., Includes typed and handwritten notes. (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Will Rice., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, dealing with the newspaper columnist Will Rice. (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - Ted Richmond., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, and correspondence dealing with writer and "Wilderness Librarian" James T. "Twilight Ted" Richmond. (Box 11, Folder 130)
    - Riddles. Folder 1 of 2., Contains typed and handwritten notes and correspondence. (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - Riddles. Folder 2 of 2., Contains typed and handwritten notes, newspaper clippings, and reprints of journal articles by Vance Randolph, Archer Taylor, and Isabel Spradley, dealing with riddles. (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - Ritual planting., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, dealing with agricultural superstitions. (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Roaring River., Contains a nine-page typescript entitled "Roaring River," which describes the Roaring River in Missouri. (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - Spider Rowland., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed notes dealing with newspaper columnist and Arkansas gubernatorial candidate Hardy "Spider" Rowland. (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - "The Honorable" Salts (J.D. Salts)., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed notes dealing with author and presidential candidate James D. "The Honorable" Salts. (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - Buck Saunders., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, dealing with gun collector Col. C. B. "Buck" Saunders. (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - Shape notes (Modal tunes, gapped scales)., Contains typed and handwritten notes dealing with shape note singing. (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - The Shibboleths., Contains typed and handwritten notes and newspaper clippings dealing the proper pronunciation of the word Arkansas. (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - Leonard Short., Contains newspaper clippings, and handwritten notes dealing with the outlaw Leonard Short. (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - Short change., Contains newspaper clippings, and handwritten notes dealing with con artists. (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - Show business., Contains newspaper and magazine clippings about the intersection of show business and the Ozarks. (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Skipping games., Contains newspaper clippings, reprints of journal articles, handwritten and typed notes, and correspondence dealing with jump rope rhymes and skipping games. (Box 12, Folder 143)
    - "Some Call it Guts.", Contains a five page typescript recounting a shooting incident that Vance Randolph was involved in as a young man. (Box 12, Folder 144)
    - Belle Starr: Correspondence. Folder 1 of 3., Contains correspondence on the subject of Belle Starr: 3/24/1930 - 3/18/1937; 1/22/1939 - 3/3/1939; 3/10/1939 - 5/26/1939. (Box 12, Folder 145)
      Belle Starr was born on Feb. 3, 1848, in Medoc, Missouri, under the name Myra Belle Shirley, to Mr. and Mrs. John Shirley after the family moved from Virginia to Missouri about 1842. She had two older brothers; one was a confederate solder. Belle was described to be rather small, pretty, vivacious and of fiery temper. She later became the head of her own gang of outlaws. The name Belle Starr was derived from one of her husbands, Sam Starr, also an outlaw, who died before Belle died. She was murdered by her own son, Ed Reed, when she beat him. Her daughter Pearl, supposedly also a "bad woman," died in Arizona. Her granddaughter showed a writer some poetry clippings and pressed flowers collected by Belle. According to a taped interview, Starr always got away, leaving men behind to be hung. See Folders 145 through 154, 257, and 262 for more information about Belle Starr.
    - Belle Starr: Correspondence. Folder 2 of 3., Contains correspondence: 6/10/1939 - 10/(n.d.)/1939; 4/3/1940 - 4/25/1941; 5/17/1941 - 5/23/1941. (Box 12, Folder 146)
    - Belle Starr: Correspondence. Folder 3 of 3., Contains correspondence: 5/27/1941 - 7/2/1941; 7/7/1941 - 3/23/1948; 5/6/1952 - 9/3/1963. (Box 12, Folder 147)
    - Belle Starr. Folder 1 of 7., Contains newspaper clippings, correspondence, and handwritten and typed notes. The folder is subdivided into the following subjects: Appearance; Charles Cummins; Ed Reed; Pearl Starr; Hugh Harp; Riley Robertson. (Box 12, Folder 148)
    - Belle Starr. Folder 2 of 7., Contains index cards, and handwritten and typed notes. The folder is subdivided into the following subjects: Index cards; assorted notes. (Box 12, Folder 149)
    - Belle Starr. Folder 3 of 7., Contains newspaper clippings, pamphlets, correspondence, and handwritten and typed notes. The folder is subdivided into the following subjects: Charles Shirley; Hands Up!; B. Babcock; Verses; Hell on the Border; Raymond Hatfield Gardner; The True Story of Belle Starr. (Box 12, Folder 150)
    - Belle Starr. Folder 4 of 7., Contains newspaper clippings, and handwritten and typed notes. The folder is subdivided into the following subjects: Calamity Jane and the Lady Wildcats; The Story of Belle Starr; pictures; references; selected bibliography. (Box 12, Folder 151)
    - Belle Starr. Folder 5 of 7., Contains newspaper and magazine clippings, and handwritten and typed notes. The folder is subdivided into the following subjects: Interviews; assorted newspaper clippings; assorted magazine articles. (Box 12, Folder 152)
    - Belle Starr. Folder 6 of 7., Contains a numbered manuscript. (Box 12, Folder 153)
    - Belle Starr. Folder 7 of 7., Contains the Shackleford Manuscript. (Box 13, Folder 154)
    - Gabby Street., Contains newspaper clippings dealing with baseball player, manager, and radio commentator Charles E. "Gabby" Street. (Box 13, Folder 155)
    - Tall tales. Folder 1 of 3., Contains articles, manuscript, and newspaper clippings. The folder is subdivided into the following subjects: "Aged in the Woods"; Tall Tales from the Ozarks; articles. (Box 13, Folder 156)
    - Tall tales. Folder 2 of 3., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, and correspondence. The folder is subdivided into the following subjects: Correspondence; notes. (Box 13, Folder 157)
    - Tall tales. Folder 3 of 3., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, and correspondence. The folder is subdivided into the following subjects: Jokes; natural occurrences; song. (Box 13, Folder 158)
    - Tall tales: Animals. Folder 1 of 3. Contains typed and handwritten notes., Topics include: Bees, bugs, birds, game, fowl, cats, cows, and dogs. (Box 13, Folder 159)
    - Tall tales: Animals. Folder 2 of 3., Contains typed and handwritten notes and newspaper clippings. Includes: Fish, frogs, horses, small mammals, squirrels, turtles. (Box 13, Folder 160)
    - Tall tales: Animals. Folder 3 of 3., Contains newspaper clippings about animals and typed notes about people. (Box 13, Folder 161)
    - This Writing Racket. Folder 1 of 2., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, dealing with ghost writing and other aspects of the writing business. Includes: Book ideas; writers (miscellaneous). (Box 13, Folder 162)
    - This Writing Racket. Folder 2 of 2., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes. (Box 13, Folder 163)
    - "Titanic Slim" Thompson., Contains newspaper clippings and handwritten notes dealing with the gambler Alvin Clarence "Titanic Slim" Thompson. (Box 13, Folder 164)
    - Travel and travelogues. Folder 1 of 3., Contains newspaper and magazine clippings dealing with various travel destinations and tourist attractions. Includes photocopies dated 1909-39. (Box 13, Folder 165)
    - Travel and travelogues. Folder 2 of 3., Includes photocopies dated 1949-57. (Box 14, Folder 166)
    - Travel and travelogues. Folder 3 of 3., Contains originals. (Box 14, Folder 167)
    - Typescripts. Folder 1 of 4., Contains student projects and a typescript of the article "Folklore of the Smackover Oil Field," including photographs. (Box 14, Folder 168)
    - Typescripts. Folder 2 of 4., Contains the following typescripts of articles: "H.H. Dalhoff, 1/19/56"; "How to Tell an Ozark Hillbilly Today"; "Folklore and Folkways of the Ozark Region"; "The Missouri Ozarks." (Box 14, Folder 169)
    - Typescripts. Folder 3 of 4., Contains typescripts of the following articles: "Ozark Superstitions"; "Racial Elements and Folklore." (Box 14, Folder 170)
    - Typescripts. Folder 4 of 4., Contains typescripts of the following articles: "Snap-Shots for Sportsmen"; "The Sport of Gigging Suckers"; "Way Back in the Hills." (Box 14, Folder 171)
    - Two Gentlemen from Verona (Harry and Jim Browning)., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, correspondence, and pamphlets dealing with the wrestler Jim Browning and his cousin Harry Browning, a poet. (Box 14, Folder 172)
    - Jean Wallace., Contains newspaper clippings and an annotated photoprint dealing with Jean Wallace, "The Mystery Maid of Roaring River." (Box 14, Folder 173)
    - The White River Monster., Contains newspaper clippings dealing with a legendary monster in the White River of Arkansas. (Box 14, Folder 174)
    - Wild Men hermits., Contains newspaper clippings, and typed and handwritten notes, dealing with hermits and recluses. (Box 14, Folder 175)
    - Thomas Williamson., Contains typed and handwritten notes about the novelist Thomas Williamson and his time in the Ozarks. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Witchcraft., Contains correspondence, a copy of "A Witch Trial in Carroll County," handwritten notes, and a typescript of "The Hills are Full of Witches." (Box 14, Folder 177)
    - World War I., Contains four typed pages of notes dealing with Vance Randolph's experiences during World War I. (Box 14, Folder 178)
    - Writers' Project. Folder 1 of 2., Contains newspaper clippings and correspondence dealing with the WPA Federal Writers' Project. (Box 14, Folder 179)
    - Writers' Project. Folder 2 of 2., Contains correspondence 1936-37 about the WPA Federal Writers' Project. (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - Correspondence Files
    - "A" Correspondence., Contains letters to and/or from: The Arkansas Gazette; The American Legion; Russell Ames; and others. (Box 15, Folder 181)
    - "B" Correspondence. Folder 1 of 2., Contains letters to and/or from: H.M. Belden, University of Missouri; Thomas Hart Benton; Walter Blair, University of Chicago; Boston University; Benjamin Botkin. (Box 15, Folder 182)
    - "B" Correspondence. Folder 2 of 2., Contains correspondence with Carroll Bowen, University of Chicago Press; Bertrand Bronson, University of California; and others. (Box 15, Folder 183)
    - "C" Correspondence. Folder 1 of 2., Contains correspondence with Irene Carlisle; Cyril Clemens; Dean Coffin Press; Columbia University; Jack Conroy; Josiah Combs. (Box 15, Folder 184)
    - "C" Correspondence. Folder 2 of 2., Contains correspondence with Henry Cowell; Sidney Robertson Cowell; and others. (Box 15, Folder 185)
    - "D" Correspondence. Folder 1 of 2., Contains correspondence with Clarence Decker; J. Frank Dobie; Dover Publications; and others. (Box 15, Folder 186)
    - "D" Correspondence. Folder 2 of 2., Contains correspondence with Richard Dorson, 1952-67. (Box 15, Folder 187)
    - "E" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with Albert Einstein; Duncan Emrich; Robert Erwin; and others. (Box 15, Folder 188)
    - "F" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with Clifton Fadiman; Orval Faubus; Charlie May Fletcher; Isabel France; and others. (Box 15, Folder 189)
    - "G" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with Henry Glassie; Kenneth Goldstein; Rayna Green; Edith Greenburg; and others. (Box 15, Folder 190)
    - "H" Correspondence. Folder 1 of 3., Contains correspondence with Leonard Hall; Herbert Halpert; Wayland Hand; A.M. Haswell; Marion Hardgrove. (Box 15, Folder 191)
    - "H" Correspondence. Folder 2 of 3., Contains correspondence with Lee Hays; Jack Henle, Vanguard Press; Wayman Hogue; Mary D. Hudgins; John Huff. (Box 15, Folder 192)
    - "H" Correspondence. Folder 3 of 3., Contains correspondence with Betty Hughes; Tom Hurley, Channel 9 KETC; and others. (Box 15, Folder 193)
    - "J" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with Moritz Jagendorf; Katherine Jarrell; LeRoi Jones; Louis Jones, New York State Historical Association; Louis Webster Jones, University of Kansas. (Box 16, Folder 194)
    - "K" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with Helen Keller; Reamer Keller; Alfred Knopf, the American Mercury; Sarah Gertrude Knott; George Korson; and others. (Box 16, Folder 195)
    - "L" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with Rose Wilder Lane; Ray Lawless; MacEdward Leach, the American Folklore Society; Sam Leath; Walt Lemke, University of Arkansas; Lawrence Levin; Homer and Wilbur Leveret. (Box 16, Folder 196)
    - "L" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with H.H. Lewis; Alan Lomax; George Dewey Lorey; and others. (Box 16, Folder 197)
    - "Mc" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with May Kennedy McCord; Judith McCulloh; and others. (Box 16, Folder 198)
    - "M" Correspondence. Folder 1 of 2., Contains correspondence with Mrs. Mahnkey; James Masterson; H.L. Mencken; George Milburn. (Box 16, Folder 199)
    - "M" Correspondence. Folder 2 of 2., Contains correspondence with Nellie Mills; Mirandy; Merlin P. Mitchell; Ethel Moore; Ruth Ann Musick; and others. (Box 16, Folder 200)
    - "N" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with N.C. Nelson; Marion Neville; Peter Nemo (pseudonym of Vance Randolph). (Box 16, Folder 201)
    - "O" Correspondence. Folder 1 of 2., Contains the Ozarks Folklore Newsletter. (Box 16, Folder 202)
    - "O" Correspondence. Folder 2 of 2., Contains correspondence with O'Bryant; University of Oklahoma Press; Jim Owens Enterprises; Clay Anderson, of the Ozark Mountaineers; Arkansas Folklore Society (originally the Ozark Folklore Society). (Box 16, Folder 203)
    - "P" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with Russell Holman, Paramount Pictures; Louise Pound, Department of English, University of Nebraska; Gerry Parker; and others. (Box 16, Folder 204)
    - "R" Correspondence. Folder 1 of 2., Contains correspondence with Gould Randolph; John Randolph (Sr. and Jr.); and others. Also contains reviews for Richard Dorson's American Folklore and Kenneth Lynn's Mark Twain and Southwestern Humor. (Box 16, Folder 205)
    - "R" Correspondence. Folder 2 of 2., Contains correspondence with Otto Ernest Rayburn, notes, newspaper clippings, and an inscribed copy of Forty Years in the Ozarks. (Box 17, Folder 206)
    - "S" Correspondence. Folder 1 of 3., Contains correspondence with Carl Sandburg; Dore Schary. (Box 17, Folder 207)
    - "S" Correspondence. Folder 2 of 3., Contains correspondence with Howard Shapley; Floyd Shoemaker; Rose Spaulding. (Box 17, Folder 208)
    - "S" Correspondence. Folder 3 of 3., Contains correspondence with Harold Spivacke; Isabel Spradley; Edward G. Stoy; and others. (Box 17, Folder 209)
    - "T" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with Jean Thomas; Shelby Thompson; Stith Thompson; and others. (Box 17, Folder 210)
    - "U" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with Lucile M. Upton; Francis Lee Utley. (Box 17, Folder 211)
    - "V" Correspondence., Contains correspondence with Vanguard Press; John M. Virden. (Box 17, Folder 212)
    - "W" Correspondence. Folder 1 of 3., Contains correspondence with Leila Wade; Therese Westermeier, Arkansas Folklore Society; John Turner White. (Box 17, Folder 213)
    - "W" Correspondence. Folder 2 of 3., Contains correspondence with Henry H. Wiggins; Thames Williamson; Charles Morrow Wilson. (Box 17, Folder 214)
    - "W" Correspondence. Folder 3 of 3., Contains correspondence with Carl Withers; Ray Wood; and others. (Box 17, Folder 215)
  - Reprints of Journal Articles and Reviews
    - "Autograph Albums in the Ozarks," by Vance Randolph and May Kennedy McCord. (Box 18 (oversize), Folder 216)
    - "Bedtime Stories from Missouri," by Vance Randolph, reprinted from Western Folklore (January 1951). (Box 18 (oversize), Folder 217)
    - "A Calendar of Kansas Butterflies," by Vance Randolph, from Entomological News (March 1929). (Box 18 (oversize), Folder 218)
    - "Children's Rhymes from Missouri," by Ruth Ann Musick and Vance Randolph, reprinted from Journal of American Folklore (October-December 1950). (Box 18 (oversize), Folder 219)
    - "The Collection of Folk Music in the Ozarks," by Vance Randolph and Frances Emberson, reprinted from Journal of American Folklore (April-June 1947). (Box 18 (oversize), Folder 220)
    - "Folksong Hunters in Missouri," by Vance Randolph and Ruth Ann Musick, reprinted from Midwest Folklore (1951). (Box 18 (oversize), Folder 221)